Guide to the Franklin Bowditch Dexter Papers
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Files on Alumni, Circa 1701-1912; Series I; 9' (22 boxes)
  - Payne, Oliver Hazard. 1863 (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Payne, Seth. 1726 (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Payson, Joshua Payne. 1819 (Box 13, Folder 151)
  - Peabody, George. 1835 non-graduate (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Pearl, Joshua F., 1836
    See: box 21, folder 252.
  - Pease, George Eleazer Holt. 1856 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Pease, John Charles. 1805 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Pease, Seth. 1846m (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Peck, Henry Edward. 1823 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Peck, Isaac. 1821 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Peck, Jabez. 1784 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Peck, John H. 1861 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Peck, William Billings. 1806 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Peckham, Fenner Harris. 1842m (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Peet, Dudley. 1852 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Peet, Edward William. 1823 (Box 13, Folder 152)
  - Peet, Harvey Prindell. 1822
  - Pell, John. 1757 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Pellet, John. 1804 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Pelton, Cole. 1840 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Penniman, Silas May. 1828 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Pennington, Charles Josias. 1846 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Penny, Benjamin Franklin. 1858 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Percival, James Gates. 1815 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Perit, John. Webster. 1801 (Box 14, Folder 153)
  - Perkins, Alfred Elijah. 1830 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, Alfred James. 1827
  - Perkins, Benjamin. 1785 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, Charles. 1813 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, Eliphaz. 1776 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, George. 1828 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, George Clap. 1861 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, George Edmund. 1843m (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, George Washington Thomas. 1846 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, John. 1840 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, John Douglas. 1791 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, Nathaniel Shaw. 1812 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perkins, Norman Carolan. 1857
    See: Palmer, Jonathan Eugene, box 13, folder 148.
  - Perkins, Samuel. 1785
    See: Williams, Timothy, box 21, folder 259.
    See: Williams General (Williams, Thomas), box 21, folder 259.
  - Perkins, William. 1840 (Box 14, Folder 154)
  - Perot, Edward. 1811 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Perrin, Edward Oscar. 1877 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Perrin, James H. 1895 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Perry, David Charles. 1833 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Perry, Frederick William. 1846m (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Perry, John McCurdy Strong. 1827 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Perry, Joshua. 1775
  - Perry, Nathan Strong. 1839m (Box 14, Folder 155)
    See: Perry, Frederick William, box 14, folder 155.
  - Perry, Samuel. 1824 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Peters, George Absalom. 1881h
  - Peters, Hugh Florein. 1849 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Peters, John Thompson. 1789 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Peters, Manly. 1827m (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Peters, William Thompson. 1825 (Box 14, Folder 155)
  - Pettengill, Benjamin Dean. 1883h (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Pettibone, Chauncey. 1806 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Pettis, Julian Vail. 1836 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Phelps, Aaron. 1758 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Phelps, Alexander. 1744 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Phelps, Benajah. 1761 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Phelps, Benjamin Kinsman. 1853 (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Phelps, Dryden William. 1876 non-graduate (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Phelps, Dudley. 1823
    See: Phelps, Benjamin Kinsman, box 14, folder 156.
  - Phelps, Guy Rowland. 1825m (Box 14, Folder 156)
  - Phillips, Andrew Wheeler. 1873p (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Phillips, George. 1769 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Pickett, John. 1705 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Pickett, Noble Bennet. 1834m (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Pierce, Franklin Williams. 1876
  - Pierce, Leonard. 1826m (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Pierpont, Daniel Hobart. 1871p (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Pierpont, Henry. 1854m (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Pierpont, John. 1804 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Pierpont, Joseph. 1751 (Box 14, Folder 157)
  - Pierson, John. 1711 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Pierson, John. 1729 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Pierson, Stephen. 1868 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Pierson, William Seward. 1808 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Pinto, Solomon. 1777 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Pinto, William. 1777 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Pitkin, Caleb. 1806 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Pitkin, Samuel. 1779
    See:Willilams General Folder, box 21, folder 259.
  - Pitkin, Timothy. 1785
    See:Williams General Folder (Williams, Timothy), box 21, folder 259.
  - Pixley, Erastus. 1780 (Box 14, Folder 158)
    See also: Tuthill, Samuel, box 17, folder 206.
  - Platt, Gideon Lucian. 1838m (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Platte, Dan. 1822m (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Platte, John Webb. 1842 (Box 14, Folder 158)
  - Pliny, Arms. 1798
  - Plumbe, William. 1769 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Plummer, George. 1804
    See: box 21, folder 253.
  - Poll, Daniel. 1869m (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Pomeroy, Benjamin. 1733 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Pomeroy, Jerome Bonaparte. 1829m (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Pomeroy, Josiah. 1762
  - Pomeroy, Josiah. 1770
  - Pomeroy, Theodore. 1808 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Pond, Charles Floyer. 1830 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Pond, Charles Hobby. 1802 (Box 14, Folder 159)
  - Poole, Benjamin. 1866 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Pope, John. 1815
  - Pope, Le Roy. 1823 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porcher, Frederick Adolphus. 1828 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Amasa. 1793 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Daniel. 1828m (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Edward Clarke. 1858 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Edward Leighton. 1857 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Henry Bliss. 1821 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Henry Clinton. 1848m (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, John. 1770 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Joshua. 1754 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Peter Buell. 1791 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Robert. 1795 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Solomon. 1775 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, Timothy. 1726
  - Porter, William Henry. 1841 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Porter, William Smith. 1825 (Box 14, Folder 160)
  - Post, Samuel Adams, Lyons Law. 1853 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Potter, Daniel. 1780 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Potter, Daniel Tertius. 1858 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Potter, Elam. 1765
  - Potter, Horace. 1804 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Potter, James. 1814 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Potter, Leander Hubbell. 1854 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Potter, William Henry. 1852h (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Potts, William Sherman. 1854 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Potwine, Thomas. 1751 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Powell, Charles Leven. 1823 (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Powell, Ferdinand Eugene. 1871p (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Powell, Joseph. 1884p (Box 14, Folder 161)
  - Powers, Henry. 1857 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Pratt, Henry Cleveland. 1857 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Pratt, Howard Eben. 1864 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Pratt, James Pepper. 1861 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Pratt, Mark. 1826 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Pratt, William Noyes. 1877p (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Prentice, Charles Theron. 1832 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Preston, Isaac Trimble. 1812 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Preston, William. 1826 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Price, Eliphalet. 1826h (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Prime, Benjamin. 1761 (Box 14, Folder 162)
  - Prindle, Chauncey. 1776 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Pringle, John McPherson. 1831 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Pritchard, David. 1832m (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Proctor, Henry Martyn. 1840 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Proctor, John. 1854 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Profilet, Louis Emile. 1857 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Prudden, George Peter. 1835 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Pumpelly, George James. 1826 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Purcell, James. 1824m (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Purnell, Lemuel. 1809 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Putnam, Charles Marsh. 1826 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Pynchon, Joseph. 1757 (Box 14, Folder 163)
  - Quick, Charles William. 1843 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Quigley, John Franklin. 1871p (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Radcliff, John. 1792 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Rae, Luzerne. 1831 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Rafferty, John Chandler. 1835 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Rains, James Edward. 1854 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Randall, Nicholas Phillips. 1803 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Raymond, David Hillhouse. 1810 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Raymond, Edward Artemas. 1844 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Raymond, Henry Augustus. 1825 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Raymond, Henry Hunter. 1841 (Box 14, Folder 164)
  - Raynor, Gilbert John. 1864 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Redfield, James. 1845 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Redfield, William Charles. 1839h (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reed, Daniel. 1778 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reed, Edmund Luther. 1823 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reed, Eli. 1822 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reed, John Taft. 1803 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reed, Stephen. 1824 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reeve, Abner. 1731 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reeve, Ezra. 1757 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reid, Horace Hall. 1843 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reily, George Wolf. 1854 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Remington, Jonathan. 1798 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Rexford, Lyman Spencer. 1808 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Reynolds, William. 1795 (Box 14, Folder 165)
  - Rice, Caleb. 1766 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Rice, James Clay. 1854 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Rice, John Parker. 1809 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Rice, Nehemiah. 1774 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Rice, Thomas. 1803 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Rich, Charles. 1838 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Rich, Samuel. 1804 (Box 14, Folder 166)
  - Richards, Frederick A. 1814 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Richards, Guy. 1807 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Richards, John. 1745 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Richards, Robert Kerr. 1827 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Richards, Samuel Thomas. 1846 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Richards, Wolcott. 1825m
    See: Richards, Guy, box 15, folder 167.
  - Richardson, Walker. 1849 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Richmond, Andrew Augustus. 1848l (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Riggs, Benjamin Clapp. 1865 (Box 15, Folder 167)
  - Righter, Clarke. 1856 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Riley, Henry Augustus. 1870 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Ripley, Joseph. 1823 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Rising, Henry Harmon. 1833m (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Ritter, Thomas. 1826 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Robb, John Hunter. 1843 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Robbins, Asher. 1782 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Robbins, George Stillman. 1818 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Robbins, James Watson. 1822 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Robbins, Levi. 1796 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Robbins, Robert. 1760 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Robbins, Samuel. 1846 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Robbins, Silas. 1808 (Box 15, Folder 168)
  - Robert, Daniel. 1810 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robert, William Smith. 1815 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Roberts, Charles Fox. 1808 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Roberts, Charles Theodore. 1879m (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Roberts, William Jay. 1859 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robins, John Purnell. 1833 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robinson, Alexander Charles. 1829 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robinson, Charles Drake. 1829 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robinson, George Chester. 1856 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robinson, Hugh. 1809 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robinson, John. 1847 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robinson, Samuel. 1817 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robinson, Stephen Thomas. 1827 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Robinson, William Wilshire. 1842 (Box 15, Folder 169)
  - Rockwell, Charles. 1826
    See: Udall, Richard Athil, box 17, folder 208.
  - Rockwell, Eliu. 1766d (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rockwell, Hubbard. 1815 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rockwell, William Hayden. 1824 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rockwood, Ebenezer Hazard. 1832m (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rogers, Ammi. 1790
  - Rogers, Charles William. 1829 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rogers, Ebenezer Platt. 1837 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rogers, George Bliss. 1880p (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rogers, George Hammond. 1850m (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rogers, John Sill. 1815 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rogers, Medad. 1777 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Rogers, Timothy. 1774 (Box 15, Folder 170)
  - Roosa, Daniel Bennett St. John. 1860h (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Root, Nathaniel William Taylor. 1852 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Root, Samuel. 1807 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rose, David. 1760 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rose, Joseph James. 1883 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rosseter, Elnathan. 1756 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rosseter, John Collier. 1756 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rossiter, William Sidney. 1815 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rowe, Charles Henry. 1862 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rowell, Samuel Newell. 1849 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rowland, James Giles. 1846 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rowland, William. Frederick. 1826 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rudd, Hezekiah. 1806 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Rudd, Samuel. 1796 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Ruggles, Benjamin. 1721 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Ruggles, Samuel Bulkley. 1814 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Runk, Charles Miner. 1845 (Box 15, Folder 171)
  - Russell, Henry Dwight. 1873l (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Russell, Jacob Wadsworth. 1860 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Russell, Joseph. 1793 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Ruthven, James Alexander. 1847l (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Rutledge, Francis Huger. 1820 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Sackett, Edward. 1857p (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Sackett, William Henry. 1803 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Safford, James Merrill. 1866h (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Sage, Sylvester. 1787 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - St. John, Buckingham. 1768 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - St. John, Eliphalet. 1791 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - St. John, Lewis. 1800 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - St. John, Samuel. 1834 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Salter, John Williams. 1818 (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Salter, Richard Henry. 1831m (Box 15, Folder 172)
  - Saltonstall, Dudley. 1791 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sampson, Ezra. 1773 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sandford, William Fiske. 1872 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sands, Henry Berton. 1883h (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sandys, Edwin Francis. 1857 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sanford, Ahaz. 1812 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sanford, David. 1803 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sanford, David. 1829 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sanford, Edward Isaac. 1847
  - Sanford, Ezekiel. 1815
  - Sanford, Hezekiah Booth. 1809 (Box 15, Folder 173)
    See also: Sanford, Ahaz, box 15, folder 173.
  - Sanford, Julius Eliada. 1839 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sanford, Peleg Phelps. 1820 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sanford, Rollin. 1831 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sanford, Whiting. 1816 (Box 15, Folder 173)
  - Sargent, Henry. 1841 (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Saunders, Alanson. 1827 (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Saunders, Ephraim Dod. 1831 (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Saunders, James Melville. 1845h (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Savage, Thomas. 1792 (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Savage, Thomas Staughton. 1825 (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Savery, Ward Webster. 1884 (Box 15, Folder 174)
  - Scarborough, Godfrey. 1829 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Schaff, David Schley. 1873 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Schermerhorn, Herman Mourus. 1883d (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scofield, Azariah. 1801 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scofield, Jared. 1801 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scott, Henry Whitney. 1863 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scott, John Witherspoon. 1827 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scott, Lauren Sylvester. 1847 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scott, Walter James. 1881l (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scovil, James. 1757 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scoville, Charles Elliott. 1830 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scribner, Matthew. 1775 (Box 15, Folder 175)
  - Scudder, Henry Austin. 1842 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Seabury, Samuel. 1748 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Searle, John. 1745 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Sedgwick, Frederick. 1849h (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Seeley, Ebenezer. 1814 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Seeley, John Edward. 1835 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Seely, Franklin Austin. 1855 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Seely, Henry Maurice. 1857 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Seely, John Frank. 1860 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Seelye, Isaac. 1796 (Box 15, Folder 176)
  - Selden, Charles. 1777 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Selden, Edward. 1783 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Selden, Edward. 1811 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Selden, George. 1786 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Selden, Henry Rogers. 1857h (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Selden, Richard Ely. 1818 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Selden, Ulysses. 1802 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Selleck, Charles Grandison. 1827 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Sellew, Welles Hamilton. 1852m (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Seropyan, Christopher Dicran. 1852 (Box 15, Folder 177)
  - Sessions, Darius. 1737 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Seward, William. 1769 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Sexton, Knight. 1759 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Seymour, Isaac Gurdon. 1825 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Seymour, John Whitman. 1837 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Seymour, Ledyard. 1792 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Shaffer, Lewis William. 1876 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Shailer, Israel. 1815 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Sharp, Charles Wheeler. 1859 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Sharp, William. 1847 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Shaw, Albert William. 1879 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Shaw, Donald Douglas. 1856 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Shaw, Joseph Laurence. 1829m (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Shaw, Oliver Abbot. 1821 (Box 15, Folder 178)
  - Shearer, Sextus. 1861 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Shears, Alonzo Groesbeck. 1856h (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheffield, Charles Joseph. 1867P (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheffield, Edward Chase. 1859 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheffield, George Washington. 1845 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheffrey, Charles Woolley. 1862m (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheldon, Abraham Curtis. 1812 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheldon, Alexander. 1787 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheldon, Daniel. 1747 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheldon, Elisha. 1730 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheldon, George. 1819 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Sheldon, Henry Kent. 1859
    See: box 21, folder 254.
  - Sheldon, William. 1822 (Box 15, Folder 179)
  - Shelton, Charles Smith. 1840 (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Shelton, Daniel Booth. 1823m (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Shelton, George Augustus. 1820 (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Shelton, Theodore Botsford. 1834m (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Shepard, David. 1766 (Box 16, Folder 180)
    See also: Brewer, Daniel, box 3, folder 23.
  - Shepard, Frederick Job. 1873 (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Shepard, Frederick William. 1834m (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Shepard, John. 1748 (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Shepard, Samuel. 1793 (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Shepard, Samuel Bruce. 1856m (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Sherpard, William Arthur. 1852p (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Shepherd, Charles. 1798 (Box 16, Folder 180)
  - Sherman, Charles Bowler. 1825 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherman, David Gould. 1842 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherman, Henry. 1829 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherman, James Tuttle. 1833 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherman, Josiah. 1765h
  - Sherman, Roger. 1787 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherman, Roger Minott. 1792 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherwood, Henry. 1818 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherwood, John D. 1839 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherwood, Justus. 1824 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherwood, Moses Aaron. 1824 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherwood, Thomas DuBois. 1846 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Sherwood, William Bonney. 1829 (Box 16, Folder 181)
  - Shipman, Thomas Leffingwell. 1818
    See: Tuttle, Timothy, box 17, folder 207.
  - Shiverick, Andrew Freeman. 1862 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Shoener, John Thomas. 1848 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Sholes, Charles Mather. 1882
  - Shortlidge, Joseph. 1880
    See: Worrall, John Hunter, box 19, folder 232.
  - Sibley, John Monroe. 1843 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Sill, Edward Rowland. 1861 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Sill, Elijah. 1748 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Sill, Elijah Noyes. 1820 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Sill, George Washington. 1838 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Silliman, Benjamin. 1796 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Silliman, Ebenezer. 1727
  - Silliman, George Bliss. 1881
  - Silliman, Gold Selleck. 1752
  - Silliman, Gold Selleck. 1796
  - Silliman, Jonathan. 1817 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Silliman, William. 1808 (Box 16, Folder 182)
  - Simonds, Ephraim. 1827 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Simons, Moses Aaron. 1809 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Sinclair, George Merrick. 1883 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Singletary, John. 1813 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Skeel, Theron. 1865p (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Skelding, Arthur Eugene. 1853 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Skinner, Aaron Nichols. 1823
  - Skinner, John Warburton. 1843 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Slack, Henry. 1848 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Slack, Henry Richmond. 1855 (Box 16, Folder 183)
  - Slade, Francis Henry. 1854 (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Slidell, Thomas. 1825 (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Smalley, John. 1756 (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Smith, Abraham Miller. 1808
    See: box 21, folder 255.
  - Smith, Aristides Spyker. 1828 (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Smith, Ashbel. 1824 (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Smith, Benjamin Franklin. 1839m (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Smith, Caleb. 1744 (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Smith, Charles Dwight. 1877p (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Smith, Charles Thompson. 1873p (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Smith, Cotton Mather. 1751
    See: Wheeler, William (1779), box 18, folder 217.
  - Smith, David Marsh. 1811 (Box 16, Folder 184)
  - Smith, Ebenezer. 1809 (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, Ebenezer Clark. 1836 (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, Elbert Jones. 1847 (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, Eli. 1849d (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, Elihu Hubbard. 1786 (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, Elihu Platt. 1785 (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, George. 1812 (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, George Hazard. 1859p (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, George Willis. 1857l (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, Grant Alexander. 1880 (Box 16, Folder 185)
  - Smith, Hamilton Lanphere. 1839 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, Henry. 1800 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, Henry. 1850 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, Horace. 1818 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, Israel. 1781
    See: May, William, box 12, folder 129.
    See: Smith, Joseph Morgan, box 16, folder 187.
  - Smith, James Allwood. 1826 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, James Mongin. 1819 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, Jarvis Johnson. 1826m (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, Jedidiah. 1750 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, Job Lewis. 1849 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, Joel Washington. 1850m (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, John. 1821 (Box 16, Folder 186)
  - Smith, John Clark. 1881
  - Smith, John Cotton. 1830
    See also: Smith, Richard (1825), box 16, folder 187.
    See also: Smith, William Mather, box 16, folder 188.
  - Smith, Joseph. 1709 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Smith, Joseph Morgan. 1854 (Box 16, Folder 187)
    See also: Smith, James Allwood, box 16, folder 186.
  - Smith, Joshua. 1833 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Smith, Junius. 1802 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Smith, Levi Ward. 1839
    See: Walker, Joseph Knox, box 18, folder 211.
  - Smith, Milo Marcellus. 1846 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Smith, Moses. 1852 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Smith, Nathaniel Benedict. 1815 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Smith, Ralph Hebert. 1888p
  - Smith, Richard. 1797 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Smith, Richard. 1825 (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Smith, Roswell. 1821 ex, 1842h (Box 16, Folder 187)
  - Smith, Sidney. 1823 (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Smith, Silas Levi. 1885d (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Smith, Titus. 1764 (Box 16, Folder 188)
    See also: Chamberlain, Theophilus, box 4, folder 34.
  - Smith, Walter. 1816 (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Smith, Water Buchanan. 1865m (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Smith, Wilder. 1857 (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Smith, William. 1719
  - Smith, William. 1745
  - Smith, William Mather. 1805 (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Smith, Zephaniah Hollister. 1782 (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Smyth, Ralph Downing. 1827 (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Smyth, Richard Edward. 1866
    See: Smyth, Walter Herbert, box 16, folder 188.
  - Smyth, Walter Herbert. 1863 (Box 16, Folder 188)
  - Sneed, Samuel Kirby. 1820
  - Snowden, Charles Blair. 1804 (Box 16, Folder 189)
  - Southall, Frank A. 1837 (Box 16, Folder 189)